I WALKED
YEAR
ONCE A
MEET
A CURTAIN TO
BEHIND
GOD
SURE
NEVER
AND I WAS
BACK OUT.
WALK
I WOULD
GAVE ME TWO
LAW
THE
FOR ONE SIN.
GOATS
THE FIRST AND
KILLED
I
INSIDE THE
ITS BLOOD
CARRIED
VEIL.
I DID NOT
SECOND
THE
KILL
ON
HANDS
I LAID MY
HEAD,
ITS
SIN OF THE
EVERY
CONFESSED
IT,
OVER
PEOPLE
IT INTO THE
DROVE
AND
TO BE LOST.
DESERT
PAY.
ONE TO
AWAY.
TO CARRY IT
ONE
I ASKED WHY
YEARS
FOR
TWO.
IT TOOK
NOW.
KNOW
I
COULD HOLD
CREATURE
NO SINGLE
HALVES.
BOTH
MAN
A
LONG AFTER ME
DID WHAT MY
JESUS
NAMED
ONLY PICTURED
GOATS
TWO
PAID,
PRICE
HE WAS THE
GUILT
THE
AND THE ONE
ON:
LAID
WAS
HATH LAID
LORD
AND THE
OF
INIQUITY
ON HIM THE
ALL.
US
HIMSELF
AWAY
HE CARRIED IT
ONCE
DOWN.
SAT
AND
FINISHED.
BEHIND
TREMBLED
THE CURTAIN I
HOUR
IN TWO THE
TORE
DIED.
HE
THE SIGN;
ONLY
I WAS
SUBSTANCE.
HE IS THE
BEHIND
TREMBLED
THE CURTAIN I
TO
TOP
IS TORN FROM
BOTTOM
WILL EVER
HAND
AND NO
IT SHUT.
SEW
PLACE IS OPEN,
HOLIEST
THE
INSIDE.
IS ALREADY
JESUS
AND
IN.
WALK